Unexpected. Unpredictable. Uncontrollable. A deadly obsession takes hold.
Enduring Love is a drama, thriller, mystery film directed by Roger Michell.
Two strangers become dangerously close after witnessing a deadly accident.
On a beautiful cloudless day a young couple
celebrate their reunion with a picnic.
Joe has planned a postcard-perfect afternoon in the
English countryside with his partner, Claire.
But as Joe and Claire prepare to open a bottle of
champagne, their idyll comes to an abrupt end.
A hot air balloon drifts into the field, obviously in trouble.
The pilot catches his leg in the anchor rope, while the only
passenger, a boy, is too scared to jump down.
Joe and three other men rush to secure the basket.
But fate has other ideas...
Joe, played by Daniel Craig.
Jed, played by Rhys Ifans.
Claire, played by Samantha Morton.
Robin, played by Bill Nighy.
Rachel, played by Susan Lynch.
Mrs. Logan, played by Helen McCrory.
Enduring Love is a 2004 psychological thriller film directed
by Roger Michell and written by Joe Penhall.
It is based on the 1997 novel of the same name by Ian McEwan.
The film stars Daniel Craig, Rhys Ifans, Samantha Morton,
Bill Nighy, Susan Lynch and Corin Redgrave.
Enduring Love was released in the United Kingdom on 26 November 2004, by Pathé.
Reviews were mixed.
The film explores themes of rescue, picnic, hot air balloon.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.